offerpalmedia.com 2010-10-05

# Privacy Policy - Offerpal Media

  |    
We hate spam more than you do! 

Thank you for your interest in Offerpal Media, Inc. ("Offerpal Media") and our web sites located at www.offerpalmedia.com, www.gamepoints.com, www.offerpal.com, and our other services, including the Offerpal Wallet Facebook application (collectively, the "Offerpal Media Platform"). Offerpal Media values the privacy of the users, subscribers, members, and others who visit and use the Offerpal Media Platform (collectively or individually, "you" or "Users"). 

By using the Offerpal Media Platform, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, please do not use the Offerpal Media Platform. 

This Privacy Policy should be read in connection with, and is incorporated by reference into, the terms of use that govern the particular Offerpal Media service you are using, which terms are located at [provide links to each set of terms ], as applicable. Your use of the Offerpal Media Platform and any personal information you provide to Offerpal Media through the Offerpal Media Platform are subject at all time to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. 

## 1\. The Information Offerpal Media Collects

User-provided Information: You may provide to Offerpal Media what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name, email address, gender, age, postal mailing address, telephone number and billing information) if you upload or download certain content or products to or from the Offerpal Media Platform, enter contests or sweepstakes, take advantage of promotions, respond to surveys, register and subscribe for certain services, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the Offerpal Media Platform. You may also provide to Offerpal Media demographic information and information related to social networking sites you use, such as the name, address and description. By using the Offerpal Wallet Facebook application, Offerpal will have access to your transaction history on the Offerpal Media Platform and user activity within some Facebook applications. 

"Cookies" Information: When you access the Offerpal Media Platform, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Offerpal Media may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Offerpal Media Platform. Both session cookies and persistent cookies can be removed. Please review your web browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Offerpal Media only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

"Automatically Collected" Information: When you access the Offerpal Media Platform or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, version of software installed, system type, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, JavaScript enablement, the content and pages that you access on the Offerpal Media Platform, and the dates and times that you visit the Offerpal Media Platform, paths taken, and time spent on sites and pages. 

## 2\. Web Beacons

Our web pages may contain electronic image requests (called a "single-pixel gif" or "web beacon" request) that allow us to count page views and to access cookies. Any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon. Web beacons are typically 1-by-1 pixel files, but their presence can usually be seen within a browser by clicking on "View" and then on "Source." We may also include web beacons in HTML-formatted newsletters that we send to opt-in subscribers in order to count how many newsletters have been read. Offerpal Media web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personally identifiable information about our web site visitors, they are just the technique we use to compile anonymous information about web site usage. 

## 3\. The Way Offerpal Media Uses Information

Offerpal Media uses the information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Offerpal Media Platform, to allow us to charge and invoice you, as well as to track user-generated content and Users to the extent necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. 

We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Offerpal Media Platform updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Offerpal Media Platform. 

Offerpal Media uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Offerpal Media Platform works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

Offerpal Media may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to: (a) automatically update the Offerpal Media application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Offerpal Media Platform, and otherwise "personalize" your experience; (c) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (d) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities 

## 4\. When Offerpal Media Discloses Information

Offerpal Media does not share your personally identifiable information with unrelated organizations for their marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Offerpal Media Platform or related sites becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction. 

We may disclose some limited User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons to: provide web site hosting, development, maintenance, support, and security services; fulfill orders; validate credit card numbers; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Offerpal Media in improving the Offerpal Media Platform and creating new services features. We generally require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. We may also disclose some limited User information to third parties in connection with processing your request to redeem Offerpal virtual currency for virtual currency or virtual goods offered by such third party. 

Offerpal Media may share aggregate statistical information gathered from you and other Users with advertisers, business partners, sponsor or other third parties. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of visitors visited a certain area on a web site 

Offerpal Media may disclose User information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner required by the requesting entity. 

Offerpal Media also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; protect Offerpal Media from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Offerpal Media Platform; enforce the Terms of Use; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Offerpal Media, our Users, or others. 

## 5\. Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to share your personally-identifiable information with Offerpal Media, in which case Offerpal Media will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Offerpal Media Platform. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences on the account applicable information page, such as "My Account - Account Settings", or "My Account � Account Information". 

We recommend you do not divulge your account password to anyone. Offerpal Media will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited telephone call or e-mail. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. 

## 6\. Our Commitment to Data Security

Offerpal Media uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Offerpal Media, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Offerpal Media makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Offerpal Media learns of a security systems breach, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Offerpal Media may post a notice on the Offerpal Media Platform if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [support@myofferpal.com](mailto:support@myofferpal.com)

## 7\. Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE OFFERPAL MEDIA PLATFORM AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Offerpal Media does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Offerpal Media learns that personally-identifiable information of persons less than 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Offerpal Media Platform, then Offerpal Media will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who uses the Offerpal Media Platform, then please contact Offerpal Media at [support@myofferpal.com](mailto:support@myofferpal.com) to have that child's information deleted. 

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children's access to certain types of material on the Internet. While Offerpal Media does not endorse these resources, we provide information about them as a public service to our community. 

  * "OnGuard Online," maintained by the [Federal Trade Commission](http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html)

## 8\. International Visitors

For Users visiting the Offerpal Media Platform from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Offerpal Media Platform will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or such other non-U.S. territory for use by Offerpal Media and its affiliates for any of the purposes described herein. In addition, because Offerpal Media operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates. By providing any data on the Offerpal Media Platform, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries. 

## 9\. In the Event of Merger or Sale

In the event that all or a portion of Offerpal Media is acquired by, spun out, or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, spin out, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

## 10\. Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically, and this will be reflected by a "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. When we modify this Privacy Policy, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you (e.g. by email or by means of a notice on our homepage or a popup upon your subsequent login). Our amended Privacy Policy will automatically take effect 30 days after we provide notice of the change, except that (i) we will not, without your consent, use your previously collected personally identifiable information in a manner inconsistent Privacy Policy in effect when we received that information, and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account ceasing use of the Offerpal Service. 

## 11\. Date Last Modified

Privacy Policy last modified on [insert re-publication date]. 

## 12\. Unsolicited E-mails

Offerpal Media does not send unsolicited e-mails to non-public addresses or to anyone who has asked us not to contact him or her. Any newsletters that we send are only sent to those who have subscribed to them. To stop receiving e-mails or newsletters from Offerpal Media, click on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail or newsletter. 

## 13\. Offerpal Media Contact Information

Please contact Offerpal Media with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: Offerpal Media Inc.,161 Mission Falls Lane, Suite 100, Fremont, CA, 94539, USA, 510.403.7300 or by email at: [support@myofferpal.com](mailto:support@myofferpal.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt. 

|    
---|---|---
